ACTWU Newsclipping Files regarding J.P. Stevens Boycott 5744
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU Newsclipping Files regarding J.P. Stevens Boycott
1934- 1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
5744
4.5 cubic feet
4.5 linear ft.
Newspaper clippings.
5699383
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 27, 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 01, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619: ACWA Records 5619/007: ACTWU Organizing Department Files
Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Labor unions -- United States; Collective bargaining -- Clothing industry -- United States; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; J.P. Stevens & Co.
5699383
- Praise of Lord is Ammunition in Testimony on Labor Law, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Daily News. August 10, 1977
- Today J. P. Stevens Tomorrow the South, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Daily News Record. August 4, 1977
- Stevens Boycott Urged in Twin Cities, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Daily News Record. January 18, 1977
- Stevens Loses 2 Motions Before NLRB Law Judge, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Daily News Record. December 14, 1976
- Stevens Files Against ACTwU, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Daily News Record. October 19, 1976
- NLRB Seeks Stevens Injunction, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Daily News. January 25, 1978
- Mrs King Asks Textile Boycott, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Daily News. March 2, 1977
- NLRB to Ask Court to Enjoin Stevens on Labor Practices (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Daily News Record. February 8, 1977
- Union Drive Against Stevens to Take New Form, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Daily News Record. February 2, 1977
- AFL-CIO Pledges to Organize Stevens, Curb Some Imports, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Daily News Record. October 28, 1977
- Retailers Fear Impact of 'Stevens Bill' on Them, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Daily News Record. November 1, 1977
- Union Leaders Forecast MFA Extension by '78, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Daily News Record. November 17, 1977
- Stevens Agent In Japan Said to Bar Imports, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Daily News Record. November 29, 1977
- Garment Workers Tell Britain: Strengthen Hong Kong Union, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Daily News Record. November 30, 1977
- NLRB Cites Stevens Again, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Daily News Record. December 8, 1977
- Profit Figure Restated by J. P. Stevens, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Daily News Record. December 5, 1977
- NLRB Authorizes Bid for Nationwide Injunction, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Daily News Record. December 1, 1977
- Stevens Hires Clark Clifford to Appeal Contempt Ruling, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- ACTWU Sues Stevens, Charging Antitrust Act, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Daily News Record. November 10, 1977
- Study Lays Union Failure in South To Workers, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Daily News Record. September 7, 1977
- SE Textile Firms Calm in Face of ACTW Call for Wage Hikes, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Daily News Record. March 17, 1977
- ACTW, Stevens: Much Talk, But Did Anyone Listen?, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Daily News Record. March 2, 1977
- Stevens Response to Union Charges Relieve Some Textile Leaders, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Daily News Record. March 7, 1977
- Finley Blasts Union as 1,500 Picket Stevens' Meeting, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Percy Fires Salvo at Stevens, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Daily News Record. February 16, 1978
- Stringent Standard on Cotton Dust Gets President's Blessing, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Daily News Record. June 8, 1978
- Stevens' Boycott Backed in Canada, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Daily News Record. June 13, 1978
- Industry, Union Hit OSHA's Proposed Cotton Dust Rule, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Daily News Record. June 20, 1978
- Textile Industry Demands Global Shipment Quotas, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Daily News Record. June 30, 1978
- ACTW Wins Victory on Public Funds, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  Daily News Record. July 12, 1978
- NLRB Calls Stevens Unfair at Woolwine, VA Plant, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  Daily News Record. December 20, 1978
- Union's Suit Seeks to Invalidate Board Election at Stevens, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  Daily News Record. November 2, 1978
- Workers' Rights Violated by Stevens, Judge Rules, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  Daily News Record. November 1, 1978
- Stevens Stuggle is Theme as ACTW Meeting Opens, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  Daily News Record. September 26, 1978
- J. P. Stevens, NLRB Reach Settlement, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  Daily News Record. September 14, 1978
- Two Articles from August 10, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  Daily News Record. August 10, 1978
  - Item 1: NLRB Drops Charges Against Stevens Plant, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Format: News clipping.
  - Item 2: UM&M To Pay Ex-Employes of Robert Hall, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Stevens Boycott Suit Dismissed by Court, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 37)
  Daily News Record. August 3, 1978
- Stevens and Union Settle Their Dispute at 2 Plants, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 38)
  Daily News Record. July 27, 1978
- NLRB Withdraws Request for Stevens Injunction, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 39)
  Daily News Record. May 1, 1978
- NLRB Strikes on New Front in Battle Against Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 40)
  Daily News Record. March 23, 1978
- Top Court Rejects Plea of Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 41)
  Daily News Record. February 22, 1978
- Stevens Home Product Sales Up, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 42)
  Daily News Record. February 2, 1978
- Nationwide Injuction Sought By NLRB Against Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 43)
  Daily News Record. January 25, 1978
- Contempt Could Mean Jail Terms, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 44)
  Daily News Record. January 20, 1978
- Daily News Record and Women's Wear Daily, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 45)
  December 9, 1977.
  - Item 1: 200 at Rally in N.Y. Protest Stevens' Anti-Union Policies, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 45)
    From "Women's Wear Daily"
  - Item 2: Demonstrators Decry Stevens Union Policies, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 45)
    From "Daily News Record"
- NLRB Judge Hits Stevens For Acting In Bad Faith, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 46)
  Daily News Record. December 29, 1977
- Two Articles from Daily News Record, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 47)
  January 31, 1978.
  - Item 1: NLRB Council Rejects Union's Stevens Appeal, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Item 2: NLRB Seeks Out-of-Court Stevens Pact, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Apparel Pension Funds Ailing and In Jeopardy, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 48)
  Daily News Record. March 6, 1978
- Stevens Dropping Hosery, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 49)
  Daily News Record. March 7, 1978
- Stevens' Data Release Nixed, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 50)
  Daily News Record. March 17, 1978
- Meany Cites Sevens as Best Reform Argument, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 51)
  Daily News Record. May 18, 1978
- Labor Dep't Row Deep-Sixes Expanded Probes of Rackets, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 52)
- ACTW Targets Conway to Quit Stevens Board, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 53)
  Daily News Record. May 22, 1978
- ACTWU Cancels Charges Against Stevens Plant, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 54)
  Daily News Record. May 23, 1978
- Organizers Enter Plants at Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 55)
  Daily News Record. May 26, 1978
- Farah is Holding 'Mis-Management' Sale at Factory, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 56)
  Daily News Record. June 2, 1978
- Group Formed for Unionization, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 57)
- J. P. Stevens Hit By Union Boycott, 1976; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 58)
  New York Post. December 6, 1976
- Daily Closeup from the Other Side, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 59)
  New York Post. February 15, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Stockholders Voting on Labor Policy, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 60)
  New York Post. March 1, 1977
- Union Pledges No Letup in Organizing Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 61)
  New York Post. March 2, 1977
- Call For Justice At Stevens Rally, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 62)
  New York Teacher. December 25, 1977
- Teachers and Labor Fight Stevens Tyranny, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 63)
  New York Teacher. March 13, 1977
- Union Bid At Stevens Gets Support, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 64)
  The New York Times. February 15, 1977
- Witnesses Denounce Tactics of Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 65)
  The New York Times. August 10, 1977
- Textile Union Fight To Organize Stevens Plant Shifts to Greenville, S.C., 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 66)
  The New York Times. October 18, 1977
- Clothing Workers Union Seek Import Penalties, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 67)
  The New York Times. November 1, 1977
- Labor and Investment of Pension Funds, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 68)
  The New York Times. November 9, 1977
- Reed Larson vs. the Union Shop, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 69)
  The New York Times. December 4, 1977
- Textile Mills Fight Imports, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Union Label Search Delay a Luncheon, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 71)
  The New York Times. December 7, 1977
- Books: Dubinsky's Life, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Moynihan Warns Apparel Industry on Labor 'Reform', 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 73)
  The New York Times. December 9, 1977
- The Humphrey-Hawkins Bill's Promise, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 74)
  The New York Times. December 12, 1977
- Two articles from The New York Times, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 75)
  December 14, 1977.
  - Item 1: Labor Meeting: Holding Operation Sans Fervor, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Item 2: Meany, On Rostrum, Belies His Age, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 75)
- The NLRB Lands on J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 76)
  The New York Times. January 1, 1978
- Black-White Split Persists a Decade After Warning, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 77)
  The New York Times. February 26, 1978
- Stevens to Withdraw From Hosiery Business, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 78)
  The New York Times. March 7, 1978
- North Carolina to Speed Brown Lung Settlements, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 79)
  The New York Times. March 15, 1978
- Chariman of Avon Leaves Stevens on Union Pressure, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 80)
  The New York Times. March 22, 1978
- Six Church Grooups Urge Support of Textile Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 81)
  The New York Times. April 20, 1978
- Labor Is The Theme In Brooklyn Church, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 82)
  The New York Times. April 24, 1978
- Embattled J. P. Stevens Adds 2 New Faces to Board, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 83)
  The New York Times. May 19, 1978
- Two Articles from June 2, 1976, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 84)
  The New York Times. June 2, 1978
  - Item 1: Jury Weighin Xerox-SCM Case, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Item 2: Taiwan Denies Textile Subsidy, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 84)
- EPA Told Cleaner Air Is Costly, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Carter, in Shift, Backs Stiff Cotton Dust Rules, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 86)
  The New York Times. June 8, 1978
- Cotton Dust Rule Issued: Both Sides Unhappy, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 87)
  The New York Times. June 20, 1978
- Breach Grows as Top Labor Official Quits U.S. Posts, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 88)
  The New York Times. December 20, 1978
- A Crack, Sort of, at J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 89)
  The New York Times. May 28, 1978
- Drive to Isolate J. P. Stevens Is Renewed, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 90)
  The New York Times. March 17, 1978
- NLRB Urges Court to Curb J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 91)
  The New York Times. January 25, 1978
- Judge Calls For Broad Sanctions Against J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 92)
  The New York Times. December 29, 1977
- Two Articles from Daily News Record and The New York Times, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 93)
  December 2, 1977.
  - Item 1: J. P. Stevens Quarter Net Up 6.8%, But Fiscal-Year Figure Fell 14.4%, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Item 2: Stevens Net Up In 4th Quarter, Down In Year, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 93)
- NLRB Plans to Seek Injunction Against J. P. Stevens in Union Fight, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 94)
  The New York Times. December 1, 1977
- North Carolina Town, Site of Labor Bill Hearing, Is Focus of Union Battle for Recognition at Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 95)
  The New York Times. August 9, 1977
- Labor Mounting Strong Campaign to Unionize South, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 96)
  The New York Times. March 17, 1977
- Labor's Textile Fight: An Echo of the 1930s, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 97)
  The New York Times. March 2, 1977
- Stevens Labor Policies Assailed at Annual Meeting, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Organized Labor is Catching on in the South, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 99)
  The New York Times. February 20, 1977
- Church Groups Support Union Drive at J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 100)
- First in the South: Former Stevens Worker Wins 'Brown Lung' Compensation, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 101)
  Press Associates. March 13, 1978
- Union Files Charges Against J. P. Stevens, 1976; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 102)
  The Wall Street Journal. November 29, 1976
- Labor Board Seeks Injunction in Suit Against J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 103)
  The Wall Street Journal. March 18, 1977
- Appeals Court Denounces Acts By J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 104)
  The Wall Street Journal. September 18, 1977
- J. P. Stevens & Co. Could Incur Stiff Fines For Labor Defiance, Court Asserts, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 105)
  The Wall Street Journal. October 28, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Is Sued by Union, Charging Misstatements of Fact, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 106)
  The Wall Street Journal. November 2, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Is Sued by Clothing Union, Citing Antitrust Violations, Conspiracy, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 107)
  The Wall Street Journal. November 11, 1977
- Future of World Trade Rules For Textiles Remains Unclear Despite 2 Days of Talks, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 108)
  The Wall Street Journal. December 6, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Is Ruled Bad-Faith Bargainer by NLRB Law Judge, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 109)
  The Wall Street Journal. December 29, 1977
- Disguised Fear? Many Textile Workers Appear to Shrug Off Labor-Stevens Battle, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 110)
  The Wall Street Journal. January 13, 1978
- Effort to Enjoin J. P. Stevens Set By Labor Agency, 1977; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 111)
  The Wall Street Journal. December 1, 1977
- Court Threatens Fines and Jail if J. P. Stevens Violates Certain Orders, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 112)
  The Wall Street Journal. January 20, 1978
- National Injunction Against J. P. Stevens Is Sought by NLRB, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 113)
  The Wall Street Journal. January 25, 1978
- U.S. Sues Seven Textile Makers to Force Them to Repurchase Tris-Treated Fabric, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 114)
  The Wall Street Journal. February 2, 1978
- High Court Bars Review of Ruling on J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 115)
  The Wall Street Journal. February 22, 1978
- Labor Unit Sets Final Standards for Cotton Dust, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 116)
  The Wall Street Journal. June 20, 1978
- J. P. Stevens Action Against Atlanta Mayor Is Dismissed by Judge, 1978; News clipping (Box 1, Folder 117)
  The Wall Street Journal. August 3, 1978
- J. P. Stevens, NLRB Settle Allegations By Textile Workers, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 1)
  The Wall Street Journal. September 14, 1978
- High Court Won't Review Decision to Fine Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 2)
  The Washington Post. February 22, 1978
- The Federal Courthouse Sweepstakes, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 3)
  The Washington Post. June 25, 1978
- The Union View of Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 4)
  The Wall Street Journal. April 10, 1978
- Review & Outlook: Labor's Blacklist, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 5)
  The Wall Street Journal. March 24, 1978
- Two Stevens, New York Life Directors Resign in Another Textile Victory, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 6)
  The Wall Street Journal. September 13, 1978
- Uncertain Weapon: Some Union Boycotts Have a Lot of Impact, But Most of Them Flop, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 7)
  The Wall Street Journal. June 26, 1978
- J. P. Stevens Chooses President of College, Lawyer as Directors, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 8)
  The Wall Street Journal. May 19, 1978
- NLRB Cancels Bid For Injunction Against Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 9)
  The Wall Street Journal. May 1, 1978
- Hanover Bank's Link With J. P. Stevens Spurs Some Unions to Withdraw Funds, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 10)
  The Wall Street Journal. February 27, 1978
- Two Articles from The Wall Street Journal and The American Banker, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 11)
  March 8, 1978.
  - Item 1: Stevens' Chairman Is Forced Off Board By Union Pressure, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Chairman and Fellow Director of J. P. Stevens Leaving Mfr. Hanover Bd.; Union Hit Interlocks, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 11)
- NLRB Sets Accord With J. P. Stevens On Employe Rights, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 12)
  The Wall Street Journal. March 27, 1978
- Textile Union Wins Round From Stevens As NLRB Judge Clears Representation, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 13)
- J. P. Stevens & Co., 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Social Awareness. January 1977.
- Number One Violator, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Off Our Backs. January 1977.
- Five Articles from Various Newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 16)
  January 6, 1977.
  - Item 1: Nader Unit, Union Say Cotton Dust Standard Too Low, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Journal of Commerce
  - Item 2: Bishop Backs Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 16)
    The Daily Times
  - Item 3: Boycott To Be Explained, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 16)
    New World
  - Item 4: March Protests Labor Policies, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 16)
    The Denver Post
  - Item 5: March Protests Labor Policies, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 16)
    The Daily Item
- J. P. Stevens and the NLRB, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 17)
  AFL-CIO Milwaukee Labor Press. January 6, 1977
- Labor Zeroes in on J. P. Stevens Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Los Angeles Citizen. January 7, 1977
- Cotton Dust Limits Scored as Ineffective, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 19)
  AFL-CIO News. January 8, 1977
- Labor Front Seen Mostly Quiet in 1977, News clipping (Box 2, Folder 20)
  The Cincinnati Enquirer. January 9, 1977
- OSHA Cotton Dust Standard Blasted By Textile Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Leader. January 14, 1977
- U.S. Proposes Fixed Levels Of Cotton Dust, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 22)
  The News and Observer. January 16, 1977
- Boycott J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Labor Tribune. January 20, 1977
- A Labor Reprsentative Speaks Out: Boycott J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 24)
  St. Louis Labor Tribune. January 20, 1977
- Stevens to Reinstate Fired Union Supporter, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 25)
  Labor Journal. January 21, 1977
- A Stubborn Battle In Roanoke Rapids, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 26)
  The News and Observer. January 30, 1977
- To All Stevens Employees, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Don't Give Your Business to a Company That Gives Its Workers The Business, News clipping (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Beware of White Sales! Don't Buy J. P. Stevens Products!, News clipping (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: J. P. Stevens Employees Education Committee, 1976; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Letter from Wilson Lambert to Committee Members. December 15,1976
  - Item 4: To All Stevens Employees, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Letter from Stevens CEO James D. Finley to Employees. January 31, 1977
- Boycott of J. P. Stevens Products Gains Momentum in Major Cities, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 28)
  AFL-CIO News. January 29, 1977
- ACTW's Stevens Boycott Comes to New York, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 29)
  Daily News Record. January 26, 1977
- For J. P. Stevens It's Cheaper to Violate the Law Than Recognize It, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 30)
  Business Week. January 17, 1977
- AFL-CIO Backs Stevens Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 31)
  Buffalo Evening News. January 12, 1977
- A Reactionary Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 32)
  Spartanburg Herald. January 10, 1977
- Leaflet Blitz to Back Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 33)
  Minneapolis Labor Review. January 7, 1977
- Boycott: Please Don't Buy J. P. Stevens Products, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 34)
  Ohio ALF-CIO Focus. January 1977
- Boycotts, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 35)
  Jewelry Workers Bulletin. January/February 1977
- Concerned Southerners Unite to Aid J. P. Stevens Workers, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 36)
  RWDSU Record. January 1977
- Clothing Workers Fight Injustice, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  Voices Community Newspaper. December 1976/January 1977
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union vs. J. P. Stevens & Co., News clipping (Box 2, Folder 38)
  United States District Court: For the Southern District of New York
- The J. P. Stevens Case No Word from New England Methodists, 1978; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 39)
  Zion's Herald. February 1978
- Boycott J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 40)
  The Catholic Worker. February 1977
- J. P. Stevens Again Cited For Anti-Union Activities, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 41)
  Pennsylvania AFL-CIO News. February 1977
- Stevens Says Doesn't Intend To Lose Battle, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 42)
  Daily Herald. February 2, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Stand Charged Yet Again With Union Busting, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 43)
  RWDSU Record. February 1977
- Stevens' Ex-Employe To Get $3,710 In Pay, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 44)
  Greenville Piedmont. February 8, 1977
- Board Oks Approaches to Organizing, Backs J. P. Stevens, R. J. Reynolds Boycotts, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 45)
  Chemical Worker. February 1977
- NLRB To Seek Injunction Requiring Stevens to Bargain In Good Faith, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 46)
  Roanoke Rapids Sunday Herald. February 6, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Charged With New Violations, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 47)
  AFL-CIO News. February 12, 1977
- Bishop Eyes Union Battle, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 48)
  Beaufort Gazette. February 15, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Gathering Support, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 49)
  The Journal of American Labor. February 4, 1977
- Religious Groups Back J. P. Stevens Campaign, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 50)
  AFL-CIO News. February 19, 1977
- J. P. Stevens: A Profile of Profits and People, 1977; News clipping (Box 2, Folder 51)
  Daily Cardinal. February 21, 1977